Olesia Pryhun

Junior front-end developer

PORTFOLIO

My detailed portfolio with pet projects: https://pryhun.me.

My GitHub account: https://github.com/Olesia-P.

My <u>last project</u>: fake online shop with a local Next.js API, connected to MongoDB.

ABOUT ME

I finished a front-end course, then I continued my studies with a mentor (experienced web developer). He provided me with support and guidance throughout the whole process.

I learned through **building projects**, making mistakes and fixing them. I used all tools possible: from docs and forums to YouTube and ChatGPT.

SKILLS

Front-end:

Back-end

MongoDB

Next.js API

Next.js

TypeScript

- React
- Redux
- Chakra UI
- Sass/Scss
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML

EXPERIENCE

Studying web development

2022-2024

English Teacher

2019-2022

Language courses

 I taught teenagers and adults English, individually and in groups, offline and online.



- +380681250102 (Telegram, Viber)
- pryhun.o@gmail.com
- Telegram: <u>@Pryhun Olesia</u>
- in <u>LinkedIn</u>

LOCATION

- Ukraine, Kyiv
- Or remote work

LANGUAGE

- English C1 (CAE Certificate)
- Ukrainian (native)

EDUCATION

Online front-end course (SheCodes)

2023

Online QA Manual course (Hillel)

2022

Kyiv National Linguistic University

Bachelor of Language and Literature (Japanese) 2015 - 2019

HOBBIES

- Jigsaw puzzles
- Coloring books
- Board games

Other
Git + Bash

GraphQL

Postman